
export const users = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "What is ToNote ?",
        answer: "ToNote is a legally binding and fully remote way to sign, notarise, and share documents with ease."
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "How do I notarise a document with ToNote ?",
        answer: `
                <p class="h6">
                    Follow these simple steps to get an affidavit or
                    request a notary session:
                </p>
                <p>
                    1. Sign up on the ToNote platform and complete your
                    profile
                </p>
                <p>
                    2. On the dashboard, you can choose to get an
                    affidavit or request a notary session.
                </p>
                <p>3. Complete the request form.</p>
                <p>4. Make payment.</p>
                <p>
                    5. Once payment is received, we will connect you with
                    a notary and let you know if your virtual presence is
                    required.
                </p>
                <p>6. Join a conference call if necessary.</p>
                <p>
                    7. The process is complete. Your documents will be
                    emailed to you or delivered to your door-step
                    depending on your choice. Delivery fees apply.
                </p>
            `
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "Which documents can be notarised on the ToNote platform?",
        answer: "Any document that needs to be the authentication seal of a certified notary or commissioner for oaths can be notarised using ToNote. You can also get affidavit documents on the platform."
    },

    {
        id: 4,
        question: "What do I need for remote notarisation?",
        answer: `
        <p>The document(s) that need to be notarized. (There are affidavit templates available).<p>

        <p>
            <ul>
                <li>A device with audio and video capabilities. </li>
                <li>A valid government–issued photo ID. </li>
                <li>A valid means of payment. </li>
            <ul>
        </p>
        `
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "How does ToNote verify my identity?",
        answer: "When you sign up, the ToNote platform uses the government-issued photo ID you provide to verify your identity."
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "How much does it cost to get an affidavit or get a document notarised on ToNote?",
        answer: "It costs #4000 for an affidavit and #8000 for a notary session for any other document.Where an additional seal is required on the same document you will be charged #4000 per extra seal."
    },

    {
        id: 7,
        question: "How much does a ToNote subscription package cost?",
        answer: `
        <p>We have 3 subscription plans, they are:</p>

        <p>
            <ul>
                <li>ToNote Basic: Free</li>
                <li>ToNote Pro: #9,900 monthly</li>
                <li>ToNote for Business: #19,900 monthly</li>
                <li>Enterprise Subscription: Custom, please contact our Sales Representative.</li>
            </ul>
        </p>
    `
    },
    // Next

    {
        id: 8,
        question: " How much does a ToNote subscription package cost? ",
        answer: `
            <p>
                We have 3 subscription plans, they are:
            </p>
            <ul>
                <li>ToNote Basic: Free</li>
                <li>ToNote Pro: #9,900 monthly</li>
                <li>ToNote for Business: #19,900 monthly</li>
                <li>Enterprise Subscription: Custom, please contact our Sales Representative.</li>
            </ul>
        `
    },


    {
        id: 9,
        question: " When can I make a request for an affidavit or get a document notarised on ToNote? ",
        answer: `
            <p>
                Requests are treated Monday to Friday, 9am to 6pm.
            </p>
        `
    },


    {
        id: 10,
        question: " What forms of identification are acceptable for remote notarisation ? ",
        answer: `
            <ul>
                <li>International passport</li>
                <li>NIN</li>
                <li>Driver’s license</li>
            </ul>
        `
    },


    {
        id: 11,
        question: "Can I get a physical copy of my document delivered to my address? ",
        answer: "Yes, you can.Just follow the prompts when you are requesting your notary session.Delivery fees will apply"
    },


    {
        id: 12,
        question: "How does ToNote vet notaries before allowing them to perform notarisations on the ToNote platform? ",
        answer: "ToNote cross references their identification document and their unique supreme court number with the relevant government databases to make sure they are certified notary publics of the federal republic of Nigeria."
    },


    {
        id: 13,
        question: "If I exhaust the maximum number of documents that I am able to send on my plan before the end of the billing cycle, can I purchase credits to send additional documents without upgrading my plan? ",
        answer: `
         <p>
           No. At the moment you will need to upgrade your plan to send more documents 
            than the specified limit. Here are the limits per plan:
            <ul>
                <li> Basic - 10 Documents </li>
                <li> Pro - 50 Documents per team member </li>
                <li> Business - 100 Documents per team member </li>
            </ul>
        </p>`
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: "How do I sign a document with ToNote ? ",
        answer: `
            <p>
                <ol>
                    <li>When on the dashboard, click ‘sign a document’</li>
                    <li>Upload the documents you want to sign</li>
                    <li>The system encrypts the document uploaded, then takes you to the signing tool.</li>
                    <li>You can add the signing annotation tool and sign the document from here.
                    Participants can be invited to sign the document from here as well.</li>
                </ol>
            </p>
            `
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        question: "What is the maximum number of signers ToNote can accommodate ? ",
        answer: "ToNote currently accepts up to ten signers per document."
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        question: "Are digital signatures secure ? ",
        answer: `
                Contracts signed using enterprise - level electronic signature processes like ours 
                are completely secure and come with a detailed audit trail of who signed and 
                when they signed. `
    },



    {
        id: 17,
        question: "How can I save my documents on the ToNote system ? ",
        answer: "All documents sent or received can be accessed in the ‘my documents’ area of the platform."
    },



    {
        id: 18,
        question: "Can I work with my team on documents with ToNote ? ",
        answer: `
                Teams can work together on ToNote using the Pro plan, or the Business and the 
                Enterprise plan.With a corporate account on ToNote, teams are able to 
                collaborate on any documentation amongst themselves
        `
    },


    {
        id: 19,
        question: "What type of documents can I upload to sign on ToNote ? ",
        answer: "You can only upload PDF files"
    },


    {
        id: 20,
        question: "As a real estate company or dealer what can I achieve on ToNote ? ",
        answer: `
                ToNote expedites the agreement execution and closing process between parties 
                during real estate transactions.ToNote makes it easy for parties to find 
                ToNote expedites the agreement execution and closing process between parties 
                during real estate transactions.ToNote makes it easy for parties to find  `
    },
    {
        id: 21,
        question: "As a financial institution what can I achieve on ToNote ? ",
        answer: `
                ToNote gives you the ability to sign, notarise, share and store documents in a 
                secure digital locker for internal or external access.ToNote also allows your 
                clients collaborate with you on a whole new level of trust.Clients will be able to 
                open accounts online, notarise and submit authenticated KYC documents fully
                online, and transact with you in a more time and cost - efficient manner
        `
    },
    {
        id: 22,
        question: "How can I contact ToNote support ? ",
        answer: `
                <div>
                    To contact support, call or send us an email.
                    <p>Phone: +2348146507035</p>

                    <p>Email: ask@gettonote.com</p>

                    You can also chat to us when you are our web app by clicking on the icon shown 
                    below. The icon will be located on the bottom right of the screen.
                </div>
            `
    },


    {
        id: 23,
        question: "Is notarising on ToNote legal in the country ? ",
        answer: `
                A combination of the Notary Act, Evidence Act and Electronic Evidence Act affirm
                that ToNote meets all regulatory standards required to operate and enable the 
                virtual notarisation of documents.For more regulatory information, send an 
                email to ask @gettonote.com.`
    },


];

export const notary = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "What do I need to do to get started ? ",
        answer: `
            
            You will need to fill a form on our website where you give us your details where 
            you will provide your government issued photo ID and supreme court number.
        `
    },



    {
        id: 2,
        question: "How do I get paid for my work? ",
        answer: `
            When you register, we collect your account details. Your earnings are transferred
            to that account at the end of each week
        `
    },
]






